If you also want to work with ICICI number
then this video
can be very helpful for you. In the video I will
tell you how to
become an insurance agent in ICICI Lombard and how to
create a profile in it. This company Kitna Maal
Zindagi, I will tell you the entire process in this video,
so let's start.
First of all you have to download this app and
go to Play Store and
search for iPartnerProf, then this is how the
interface will be visible in front of everyone.
After clicking on it, I will click on Open.
After clicking on it, you have to enter
your mobile number here.
Click on Get OTP
and after that an OTP will be sent to your mobile number
and after filling it,
click on Verify and Process, then
this kind of interface will appear in front of you.
I should have completed my profile in advance,
so all these options should be there. If you
log in for the first time, then all these
options will not be shown to you, so you have to
go to My Profile and click on it, after that
click on Account Details and you have to verify all your
information.
All my information  Keep verified,
hence the greeting is visible
everywhere here, verify benefit verify a
9th, in personal details you have to
choose your name, father's name, male or female gender,
select its date of birth, mobile number, email ID and communication address,
enter the rough pin code and continue, then
it will be verified, after that for
verification you will have to upload a fixed JPG image of your PAN card
and you will have to upload the PAN number,
in the press form you can enter your electricity
bill
or your bank passbook,
on payment details you have to continue by entering your
account number, account
holder's house number, its IFSC code and
account holder's name,
then your payment proof will be
verified, after that in mode of
business you have to
select digital here and continue,
here you
can read all the terms and conditions in terms and conditions, after
all the details of your account are verified, you will have all
these options and you will get the
license number  It will also be provided which is
shown in this image,
here you
can create your let by clicking on let, here you
can also see your pending payment, in this app
you are provided two types of service providers,
one is car charger and two wheeler
insurance, here if you face any problem
then the assistant will call you
and you are subscribed on the number of an assistant
and the biggest advantage of this is that this
is an online platform and there is no
need to do any offline paper work in it,
if you liked the video then like the video
and subscribe to the channel